<?xml version="1.0"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Fraser's Newsletter</title><link>https://worldpeace.services/newsletter</link><description>Welcome to my newsletter! I started making this website at the start of 2025 and I've enjoyed growing it to where it is today. I get that it's hard to constantly check the site for updates, so to make things easier for you guys, I've prepared a newsletter which features all the new content from the website whenever I update it. If you're struggling to read the RSS feed it's fine, I get it. You can just read it directly on my website! https://worldpeace.services/newsletter</description><language>en</language><item><title>It's pretty alright, pretty cold</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-13-01-2026</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Berlin has been hit by a pretty real cold snap this month, and I've found myself super enjoying it. I'm out and about a lot, and I'm appreciating the -6 more than usual. I feel like in this age of climate change, mother nature will be telling us that she doesn't fuck around more and more often, and I'm kinda on her side. Luckily with my lifestyle I'm only ever really out in the biting cold wind for some moments before I can enter a warm building. Some of those feedback loops are going to start hitting soon when it comes to climate change, which I'm not very excited about. But Jack being so optimist when talking about the world's issues made me feel bad about dooming so much this week so maybe in 2026 we can all get excited about the prospect of nuclear fusion working. That would be sick.<br>I've thoroughly enjoyed this time around new years not just because of the cold though. Weyes put on not one but two great parties, and I actually had a bunch of time at home, so I finally got round to playing Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, which I loved. I can't wait to take some holidays from work exclusively to play games like this. That's where the priority is this year (sorry, Mexico).<br>Guys, I've spent a bunch of time on the daily soundtracks part of this website - you should check it out! There is an archive of all the previous daily soundtracks I've featured, and you can listen to them directly on the site, and even organise the tracks into little playlists. Doing this was very excited but now I'm suddenly aware that it's more important than ever that I only recommend the best songs ever. Luckily I'm overflowing with ideas about which music to recommend, and I've already made posts all the way into March. Anyway I hope it offers a fun reason to come back to the website from time to time.</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 10, Platform: Playstation 5, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Wow! I have not played a game with such good art direction as this! Whoever they hired to design the outfits needs a raise. This game is so aggressively French and I'm so here for it. It's got berets, famous landmarks, and I just went ahead and played it in French for the full experience. Loved it. And the environments look so gorgeous and detailed and have amazing lighting and yeah this game just looks amazing.<br>And sounds amazing! Excellent, expansive soundtrack, unafraid to use accordion.<br>I think the best thing about the game though is the writing. It features characters who have actual empathy for one another! And when some crazy shit happens, they take a moment to talk about it. The characters are all distinct, flawed but likeable, and have their own reactions to everything. I love that Lune just wants to ask questions about everything because the story is so wild, she's just like me. And then Sciel is like the adult in the room, aware that the world around her is bigger than what she understands and decides to be chill about the whole thing. Maelle has a moment where she was like, this is not at all what I expected and I dunno I just thought it was so real, even if her scenes were a little hard to take seriously because I gave her a ridiculous haircut.<br>The gameplay is also good. It took me a long time to get into the parrying but towards the end of the game I started getting good at it. What's nice is that there are ways to play where you don't bother with the parrying at all. It meant I didn't feel like a total noob as I was starting the game. I will say that there is some optional content where you have to do platforming and it's totally bullshit. It was worth it to get the outfit of Verso just in his trunks though.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/clair-obscur.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Wario Land 3</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 6, Gameplay: 8, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 2000</em></p>
            <p>Playing this game was so refreshing, it was familiar because I played and loved Wario Land 4, but also quite different to that game, and so different to your average platformer. In this game you can't die! It's more of a puzzle game - 'how do I get to this treasure chest?' rather than 'can I get to this treasure chest?'. I like all the transformations and the role they play in the puzzles. The game even has metroidvania elements the way you get new power-ups and revisit old levels.<br>The animations are also a lot of fun. It's such a goofy game. Delightful and recommended gem on the Nintendo Switch Online!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/warioland-3.png">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Ball X Pit</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 6, Gameplay: 8, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>This is so so so addicting, just like Vampire Survivors. Loved getting absolutely absorbed by it this Christmas. The ball part has some great risk/reward or push/pull and feels great. The city building part is a bit intimidating but actually alright in the end. I don't love the overall vibe and design of it, nor do I love the music. It's kinda gruesome and unpleasant. Honestly by the end I was happy I rolled the credits and I could stop.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/ball-x-pit.webp">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>The Legend of Zelda: Four Swords</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 6, Gameplay: 7, Platform: Gameboy Advance, Release: 2002</em></p>
            <p>Always wanted to play the multiplayer Zelda games and was finally able to when Oscar Andrew and I connected out Switch 2s on the NSO app and played local multiplayer. It was awesome and we blazed through the game in one sitting! It was consistently funny to bump into each other going through little corridors and hitting each other and we loved the whole thing. There were a couple of head-scratching moments and we weren't a fan of the mysterious Rupee Wraith. We just played it through once but it turns out that there's a true ending if you play it through on harder modes two more times. I feel like there's a lot of fun to be had here! The levels are even procedurally generated before that was cool. There's also a fun competitive element where the person who got the most rupees wins, Super Mario 3D World style. Loved that! Loved the game to be honest. Great.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/zelda-four-swords.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 6, Gameplay: 6, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1992</em></p>
            <p>I enjoyed this game on the Nintendo Switch Online! Not as fun as other Mario games because of the small screen but glad to have played this one that I always missed. Cool that this is the first appearance of Wario!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/super-mario-land-2.webp">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Metroid Prime 4: Beyond</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 6, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>This game started off so strong but by the end I decided that it isn't a true continuation of the excellent Metroid Prime series. Music and atmosphere is definitely great, although the only really memorable music is the first area, Fury Green. I feel like the game could benefit from more music tracks as actually most of the game is spent with just ambient noise.<br>The thing that I appreciate the most is that it takes place on a planet where the architecture is so yonic! Yonic is a fun word that means 'relating to vaginas and stuff' (as opposed to phallic). Every door, switch, building looks like female genitalia. Samus is going around controlling clits with her new psychic powers and you can't convince me otherwise. There is some pretty strong lesbian energy.<br>I also enjoy how so much random-ass shit happens in this game. When you beat one of the yonic bosses and then this pedestal appears which transports Samus to a dream realm where she grabs a magic key and then curls into a ball and learns how to boost up halfpipes. All that happens within like 2 minutes of each other.<br>Samus is a badass lone hunter who really doesn't need anyone else, but they introduce some annoying American characters who are stranded there anyway. I appreciate that they speak to Samus like she is a divine legend, and that Samus doesn't dignify them with any response, but ultimately they have been added as plot devices to try to add emotional weight to the story. It feels fake as fuck. It's just typical tropes like sacrificing yourself (and then turning up later), and has been totally shoehorned in. Would have been better if she was just on her own as usual. The best Metroid atmosphere is the feeling of loneliness. I don't want to get a cool new item and then immediately get a call from an American man saying where I should go next.<br>There's also a desert area where you drive around on a motorbike, a bit of a departure from the series, and it's fine, I guess. I actually appreciate how it makes it a bit more feasible to have these different climates (jungle, icy mountain, volcano) all in the same place. In Metroid Prime 1 you just hop between these biomes in a couple of seconds. That always bothered me!<br>Well, it would have been fine, except that at the end of the game, you have to drive around the desert and collect a bunch of these green crystals in order to progress to the end of the game. When it dawned on me that I only had half the crystals necessary, my heart sank. I then spent like an hour driving in this empty ass, shitty desert crashing into crystals over and over, just for the privilege of watching the ending? Bullshit. Hated it. Felt like work!<br>Then the ending, you don't even learn what Sylux’s whole deal is, unless you go for 100% (fuck that). I watched the secret cut scene on YouTube and well yeah that is a ridiculous backstory.<br>The gameplay itself was just the same as Metroid prime 1. I think they could have done more backtracking in a good way. The backtracking felt quite forced (American man tells you where to go), and how come we never return to the best place, Fury Green?<br>All in all, I'm pretty disappointed in this game and wouldn't recommend it. Play Metroid Prime 1 remastered instead!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/metroid-prime-4.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Carrie</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1976</em></p>
            <p>The first half of this classic film was unbearable to watch, but from the iconic moment at the school prom onwards we were just screaming 'Yeeees fuck em up!! Burn it all down!'. If only this is what happened when people treated women so badly in real life.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/carrie.webp">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>The Great Escape</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1963</em></p>
            <p>The family has this on the TV at Christmas quite a lot. It was alright. Got me thinking if the Germans have some kind of equivalent.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/great-escape.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Aftersun</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2022</em></p>
            <p>Story of a dad taking his 11 daughter on holiday, trying to keep it together. I felt a real connection to him because he's my age. It all felt very real.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/aftersun.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Nickel Boys</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Very upsetting film about a segregated youth detention centre where horrible shit went down. POV camera the whole time makes it all feel like it's happening to you.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/nickel-boys.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Mario & Luigi: Brothership</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This soundtrack is definitely the biggest and most pleasant surprise of the app so far. I honestly thought it would be super generic music, similar to Princess Peach Showtime or something, but actually this music is gorgeous! You can tell from the soundtrack alone that the game was made with love, which is very important to me. The strength of these tracks is so good that I'm lowkey thinking about playing the game because of it, even if I was never a bit fan of the series (well I only ever tried Superstar Saga).<br>The battle theme is insanely good, and some of these tracks have stunning chord progressions (my weakness), like 'An Afternoon on an Islet' - what an incredible little tune. I was totally ready to dismiss this soundtrack but I've listened to the whole thing twice in one day and I have to say I love it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/mario-luigi-brothership.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Fire Emblem: Path of Radiance</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Gamecube, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I have always felt like this and Radiant Dawn's soundtrack sound a bit cheap and tinny thanks to their choice of orchestra sounds. Maybe it would slap more with a real orchestra but alas the game came out in 2005. Although all my actual favourites are on the Radiant Dawn soundtrack, there are still a whole bunch of great tracks here too. And even though a lot of the music sounds the same, there is some very special music here.<br>Some of the battle music is very lengthy and epic and multi-phased (thinking about the amazing 'Crimea Attacks' - which features in the Subspace Emissary!). Then you've got 'Against the Black Knight' which is so fucking good and perfect music for fighting an unbeatable foe. And there's this horrible character called Oliver who has his theme played on the harpsichord which is such a vibe. It's giving Castlevania and I love that.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/fire-emblem-path-of-radiance.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Wii Party</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Wii, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>We are treated to some more obscure Wii-era vibes with this game that probably nobody played. Deep breaths, there's no point being upset about it, I'm sure the actual good game soundtracks will all come in 2026. This one is a bit of a slog, similar to Mario Party, but there are some gems in there. Some of these tracks like 'Garden Gridlock' really evoke 2007 hard.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/wii-party.jpg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>Shoutouts to 2025</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-20-12-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Merry Christmas! Welcome to the last newsletter of the year. I'm super happy to present my end of year list of video games. You can find it by going to the 'games' section and clicking '2025'. It's in order and yep, I put Hollow Knight Silksong at the top. What an amazing game!<br>I love lists, and ultimately that's why this website exists. It just feels so satisfying knowing I'm documenting everything in my life here. Did you know I also keep a daily diary? It's a little too personal for this website but I really recommend all readers to start one. It helps with the feeling of life running away from you.<br>It's been a particular pleasure to go to such lengths to document my life this year because this year is definitely the best of my life. It started with a super fun and life-changing trip to Mexico in January, then I continued working my excellent job which I really appreciate. I got a boyfriend! 2025 is also the year of the Nintendo Music App, which I have loved so much. It's something I've wanted since I was a child. And it's the year of this website! Working on this website has been a great learning experience and so so so fun. I'm so proud of it.<br>You guys have any new year's resolutions? Mine is to stop saying 'having time' and instead say 'making time'. I think saying 'I will try to make time for that' sounds more positive than 'I hope I have time for that' and will go far towards making me sound less like the calendar bitch that I actually am. My other resolution is to take more holidays from work when I feel like I have no time. There's no big Mexico month this year so I'll be focus on me a bit more this year.<br>See you guys next year!</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Metroid Prime 4: Beyond</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 9, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>This game is a true continuation of the excellent Metroid Prime series! Music and atmosphere is 100% there. As I write this I'm only half-way through the game so take this with a grain of salt for now, but it's great so far.<br>I really appreciate that it takes place on the planet where the architecture is so yonic! Yonic is a fun word that means 'relating to vaginas and stuff' (as opposed to phallic). Every door, switch, building looks like a vagina. Samus is going around controlling clits with her new psychic powers and you can't convince me otherwise. The game features some weak men who speak at you with American accents, but Samus doesn't even bother replying, which I really appreciate.<br>I also enjoy how so much random-ass shit happens in this game. When you beat one of the yonic bosses and then this pedestal appears which transports Samus to a dream realm where she grabs a magic key and then curls into a ball and learns how to boost up halfpipes. All that happens within like 2 minutes of each other.<br>There's also a desert area where you drive around on a motorbike, a bit of a departure from the series, and it's fine, I guess. I actually appreciate how it makes it a bit more feasible to have these different climates (jungle, icy mountain, volcano) all in the same place. In Metroid Prime 1 you just hop between these biomes in a couple of seconds. That always bothered me! Anyway, I'm excited to see how this game develops, for now I'm excited to keep playing over Christmas.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/metroid-prime-4.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Keeper</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 4, Platform: Xbox Gamepass, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>This game is like concept art come to life. It's got that Gris/Ori vibe of being beautiful for the sake of being beautiful. You play as a sentient lighthouse, which is a great premise, but ultimately it's another walking simulator with light puzzle elements. This one is different from other ones because it has amazing colours and psychedelic visuals. But ultimately, it's more of this same stuff. It makes me think that we really have enough indie games these days. Devs really have to stretch the imagination to think of new premises for new beautiful walking simulators these days.<br>I think it would be good to play this while on mushrooms.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/keeper.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Kirby Air Riders</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 8, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>So delightful to play another Sakurai game! The smash vibes are very strong in this game. The soundtrack is pretty good, with an absolute banger of a menu theme, and the levels you race on are crazy cool. You can play as Rick the hamster, which is amazing, but I'm a little broken-hearted that you can't play as Kine the fish.<br>Controlling is kinda hard! This isn't baby mode like Mario Kart World (which I loved), you have to get a feel for it. Having both sucking in enemies and drifting being the same button is kinda confusing though. Also, there's an attack you can do if you wiggle the stick, which confuses me quite a lot. I really connected with the Road Trip mode, which in effect taught me the game. Thanks to that I tried out all the machines and got a hang of the drifting. I think my favourite is the Rocket one where you have to charge to the max each time. It's extreme but satisfying!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/kirby-air-riders.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>The Secret Agent</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Vibes-heavy Brazilian thriller featuring (truly) the best female characters and the worst male characters. I struggled to keep up with the plot and the events towards the end felt a bit random.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/secret-agent.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Bugonia</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Oh my god I loved this film so much. It was wild and hugely entertaining. Conspiracy theorist meets powerful CEO and the dialog between them is just perfect. Best ending ever</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/bugonia.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Super Mario Land</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Gameboy, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This gameboy soundtrack actually has some classic bangers. It has inspired me to make a 'best bleeps and bloops' playlist. Birabuto is the classic but I am loving Muda Kingdom!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/super-mario-land.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Yoshi's Crafted World</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow this soundtrack is tragically bad. They've gone for the little kid aesthetic to the max, recorders and all, and it honestly sounds terrible. Lowlights include 'Yoshi's Expedition' and 'What's It Gonna Be?', both of which sound like infants trashing a music schoolroom.<br>The soundtrack has two saving graces! The uncharacteristic 'A Teeny, Tiny Universe' which is good because it sounds like it came from another game, and the very last track 'Round and Round' which I guess is meant to be a joke but it low-key a bop.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/yoshis-crafted-world.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Metroid Prime 4: Beyond</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow these tracks are super long. I love a lengthy loop, especially when you know that you're gonna be hanging out in a place for a long time. The vibes appear to be there, so I'm excited! At the time of writing, I've just started the game and experienced the majesty of 'Fury Green' in game. I think it's gonna be a banger.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/metroid-prime-4.jpeg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Visit to Müritz</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/lake.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Smash Tournament in Frankfurt</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/duckhunt2.jpg">
        

            <h2>New CD</h2>
            <h3>Shoot Your Shot Anthology</h3>
            <p><em>Artist: Divine</em></p>
            <p>Victor got me this amazing CD of cunty pop tracks from the legendary Divine! Perfect for pre-drinks for the party</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/albums/divine-shoot.jpeg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>Entitled to Nintendo Music</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-25-11-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hey everyone, it's me again. Quick update about the website: I added some TV shows to the Films section. I also made a tierlist of every pokemon! It was a lot of fun and it took me a whole morning. I'm thinking about slowly ranking the pokemon within the tiers later, but we'll see. Interestingly, for that page I added over 1000 images to the website and it hit me that this website in total has around 3000 images, and a bunch of mp3s on the music page. I then spent an entire afternoon and evening reorganising my images and assets and now the website is lightweight again! Even myself I feel a little spring in my step, like a burden has been lifted from my shoulders. Anyway, on to today's main topic...<br>As regular visitors of this site might know, my year has been drastically improved by the appearance of the new Nintendo Music App. One of the biggest parts of this site is my weekly reviews of each new release. I love it so much, I've even started observing a strange kind of mysticism in which the kind of soundtrack released on a Tuesday dictates what kind of week I'm going to have. As somebody who doesn't tolerate astrology I know that it's bullshit but I can't help but think about it whenever I am delighted or disappointed by a particular release.<br>It's a very niche interest. Not many people I know love Nintendo music to the extent that I do. It means it's a struggle to find people to be enthusiastic about the release on Tuesday with. That's why I'm eternally grateful to my two mates from home, Oscar and Andrew, who are actually willing to discuss and rate each soundtrack when it comes! We have a little Whatsapp group for it and I honestly love it so much. As I write this, I'm listening to the Wii Fit soundtrack, which is full of surprising bangers, thinking that my week has the potential to be 'surprisingly good' and in general appreciating this era of Nintendo music vibes. It's so good.<br>Recently I found myself wondering if anyone else out there is living their lives week to week like me, just waiting for the next release. Surely there are others who have spend the last decades lamenting the lack of official releases of these classic soundtracks? Surely other people are as excited as me by having a full on feature-rich app with a bunch of these OSTs on them, having them drip-fed to us? So I went onto reddit.com.<br>I've been on reddit.com a couple of times and I almost always have a bad time. I get that it has real people on there, one of the few places left that does. But everytime I visit I'm reminded how they're all Americans there, and they're all Negative Nancies. They just complain! I found a subreddit r/nintendomusic where there is a bunch of spam, and then each week a thread about the week's release in the app. Excited I clicked on Wii Fit's release and all I see are a bunch of sarky comments about they don't get a real soundtrack like Mario or Zelda, how shit the app is, etc. etc.<br>This bothers me so much because a) the app comes free with the already insanely cheap Nintendo Switch Online subscription. They were paying for this thing already and then bam, free music app to go with it. Then with each release, they go onto reddit.com and complain! They feel entitled to more. Why not release the app with all the soundtracks on it already? How dare they release Wii Fit when Majora's Mask isn't even on there yet? These keyboard warriors need to calm down, do some deep breathing and just enjoy the Wii Fit soundtrack.<br>I mean I too have been disappointed by the initial catalog and certain releases (looking at you OOT 3D and Metroid 2) but I've learned to appreciate what I'm given. Occasionally there is an amazing release (Paper Mario, TOTK) which catapults me into two weeks of reliving those games and I love it so much. If they gave us everything from the beginning for free, I don't think I would be as hooked on the app as I am. Also, I have to say that as an app developer myself I get it. Making features takes ages and writing content takes ages. These soundtracks all have screenshots as artwork, playlists associated with each track, and all the work behind getting the soundtracks themselves. It's a bunch of work and I get it.<br>Maybe people feel entitled to this music because it's all available on Youtube for free already. That's fair enough, and to be fair, only on this one subreddit I actually found any discussion on it. I think most people completely ignore this app. Anyway, at least there's one website covering these important releases!<br>Here's hoping that it continues, becoming an exhaustive bank of great music over the coming years. I'll be there every step of the way. Love live the Nintendo Music App!</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>CloverPit</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 8, Platform: Xbox Gamepass, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>A cool vibe from a hellish gambling game where it's not actually about gambling, it's about optimising and finding bottlenecks and scaling numbers. It's actually just Balatro. It's Balatro all over again with a slot machine instead of poker hands. Fab and I got a really good run on our first run because we got some great synergies with diamonds. I'm interested to keep playing to know if it's possible to leave the room but something tells me it's not. Cool game, just would have been better if it were released BEFORE Balatro...</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/cloverpit.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Kirby's Dream Land 2</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 7, Gameplay: 5, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1992</em></p>
            <p>This is the kirby game with the 3 animal friends. You spend most of the game riding them and honestly I think it detracts from the experience a bit.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/kirby-dream-land-2.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Survival Kids</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 7, Gameplay: 4, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1999</em></p>
            <p>I saw that they realised a newer Survival Kids game, but only on the Nintendo Switch Online did I see that it's a long series with a Gameboy release in 1999! Turns out, this game might be the first ever survival-type game. Probably the reason why games like 'Don't Starve' exist. So for science I booted it up and gave it a good try.<br>First, I was pleasantly surprised by the banger music. Always a great sign when the OST ist good. I was looking for materials while grooving to the max. It's almost as if the child that I'm playing as hasn't been stranded alone on an island! Considering it's a game about not dying, it's surprisingly peppy and fun. The intro story was funny, it said the child and their dad were the only crew on the boat when it was shipwrecked, and then it shows just a massive cruise ship sinking. No wonder it sank - there were only two people on board!<br>I didn't make it far in the game, regrettably. It hit me that there's a reason that I didn't enjoy 'Don't Starve'. At any moment, my hunger or thirst could drop to zero and then bam, I have to start the whole game again! That is so stressful. And the game really doesn't do any signposting at all. I don't think it's possible to actually complete it without some kind of guide.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/survival-kids.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Kirby's Dream Land</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 8, Gameplay: 6, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1992</em></p>
            <p>I managed to beat this entire game while Victor took the dog out! It was delightful, although actually a little harder than your usual Kirby game because there were no broken copy abilities. Great to see the origin of so much Kirby stuff. Loved the King Dedede fight in which he used dash attack, up special, f-smash, neutral special. Great. Music is also 10/10.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/kirby-dream-land.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Ristar</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 8, Gameplay: 6, Platform: Sega Mega Drive, Release: 1995</em></p>
            <p>I had vaguely heard of this game so I gave it a go on the Nintendo Switch Online and was delighted by the amazing soundtrack. The game itself was quite forgiving for a mega drive game! Although as a platformer it's nothing special. I'm grateful that I now know about its great OST though.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/ristar.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Ecco the Dolphin</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 4, Platform: Sega Mega Drive, Release: 1992</em></p>
            <p>I've been aware of the soundtracks of these games, made by Tim Follin, one of my favourite composers, for a long time. They are baffling, expansive and vibe-heavy games in which you play as a dolphin! Truly a first in the dolphin genre. I also heard that they are hard as balls so I was curious, and indeed, it's hard as balls. It's totally confounding and has no information about where to go or what to do. You just swim around and die to random things all the time. Definitely the kind of game to just listen to the soundtrack to and not actually play.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/ecco-the-dolphin.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Streets of Rage 2</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 9, Platform: Sega Mega Drive, Release: 1992</em></p>
            <p>Ever since falling in love with Streets of Rage 4, I've been meaning to get into this game as well, and I'm so glad I did! The reason to open up this game on the Nintendo Switch Online is so you can listen to one of the best soundtracks of all time. It's inspired by house and techno music and each track is a fucking banger. I have literally DJ'd some of these tracks before (Go Straight and Dreamer) they are that good. They hold up today!<br>The opening music is the biggest vibe ever, although booting up the game I realised you can't actually listen to the whole opening track before the opening ends. Devastating. But it's fine because it gets straight into 'Go Straight', the most incredible first level music ever. Perfect music to beat up goons to. It's a bombastic house anthem that turns into the jazziest remix of itself when you enter the bar halfway through the level. Then in later levels you have 'Slow Moon', 'Dreamer'... just banger after banger.<br>The game itself is doable! I got to stage 7 or so using my fundamentals from Streets of Rage 4 which felt great. I quickly realised Blaze's flip move does crazy damage. But the difficulty curve is tough, it doesn't fuck around. I think it's fine because back then these arcade-style games needed to have that replayability, and this really does. You play over and over until you know all the levels back to front, and can beat them with all the characters. Part of me wishes I was into this game as a child.<br>It also has a really lovely co-op mode! Victor and I played together for a bit and it was awesome. Super fun to play with a second person.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/streets-of-rage-2.webp">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>One Battle After Another</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Such a great film. Thriller that takes you places! So many amazing moments and great characters. I'm going to chuckling about Christmas Adventurers for a while now.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/onebattle.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Frankenstein</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>They decided to make the monster hot and I don't understand why! I thought it was all pretty dumb. I guess it was entertaining</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/frankenstein.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Absolutely Fabulous</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1992-2004</em></p>
            <p>Love love love this show. Patsy is everything. It's so outrageous and camp and funny and I'm obsessed. Some stuff has aged very badly but it's worth it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/abfab.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Super Mario Party Jamboree</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow this soundtrack really is the definition of 'All Filler No Killer'. I make the time to listen to each soundtrack beginning to end but this is the first time since Splatoon or Sword/Shield I'm thinking about skipping out on that duty - because it's over 6 hours!<br>Who am I kidding I'm spending all of this Tuesday evening listening to it. The music isn't memorable but there are some gems amongst all the dirt.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/jamboree.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Wii Fit</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Wii, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>At first I rolled my eyes at this release but then I remembered that the Wii Fit soundtrack slaps. Of all the Wii-era Nintendo 'frutiger aero' music there is, this soundtrack is one of the most quintessential. Some of these tracks evoke the Nintendo Wii so hard it hurts. When I have those days when I just want to soak myself in that nostalgia, I know I can just turn on the top tracks from this soundtrack and be warped back to 2008.<br>Some of these tracks are so outrageously Wii-era that it hurts. The best example is 'Tilt City', this track blew me away. It sounds like what Windows Vista looked like. Then there's 'Rhythm Parade (Advanced)' - the beginning I don't love but then it just keeps developing and changing throughout its almost 4 minute runtime. It's so good. And what is going on with 'Bird's-Eye Bull's-Eye' and why does it sound like that? Why is it so good? That track sounds like it could be from Pikmin 3. Also, the original credits theme so weird and hypnotic, almost creepy. I can't get enough of it.<br>Some of the not amazing but still quite good ones like 'Hoop Dance' and 'Skateboard Arena (Free Mode)' got banger remixes in Smash. They really outdid themselves for those, you should go listen. We should all be selecting more Wii Fit music when playing on Small Battlefield.<br>I need to express my dismay at one small thing though. Arguably the biggest banger of the soundtrack, 'Advanced Step' got shafted in this release by being the in-game version. It's slow as fuck and speeds up half way through. PLEASE do yourselves a favour and listen to the proper one: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4_Ir6zA10w0. This is the version they included in smash. It's a huge hit!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/wii-fit.jpg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>10 out of 10</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-12-11-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hey everyone, it's me again for another newsletter! First of all, thank you to all the people who actually subscribed to the RSS Feed. I don't have a way of knowing who actually did that, but if you did, kudos! You have my respect!<br>Recently I've been telling lots of people about my theory that in Germany ratings out of 10 always amount of a 7, and sometimes a 6 if it's bad, or an 8 if it's good. When I say that my food at the Kantine at work is a 2/10, my colleagues are very shocked. Likewise, they don't let me get away with saying the food is a 10/10. They say, it might be good but surely you've had better food than that? Maybe I did, but in this moment, I enjoy the food to the max! So how can it be anything other than a 10?<br>I truly feel that rating things 10/10 makes you appreciate the nice things in life more.<br>As a little life update I'm still waiting for summer to finish in the sense that I do less shit and have more time to chill at home. I am still doing so much shit that I miss being a teenager when I had no responsibilities. I'm a little anxious about our smash tournament at Games Ground this week and I'm excited for next year when I have holiday days to spend.<br>As a little website update, I added a section for concerts! I also spent ages brainstorming all the concerts I've ever been to. I'm missing some, and I didn't include artists I saw at festivals, but it might be a nice resource if you want to compare music tastes. Maybe you were at one of these concerts? I also put the ones in the future that I have tickets to. Let me know if you're going too!<br>Finally I am still posting music recommendations each day, and now the list is getting longer. Something tells me I will need to implement more filters on that page soon. Anyway, here is all the new content on my website since the last newsletter, see you next time!</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Luigi's Mansion</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 8, Gameplay: 5, Platform: Gamecube, Release: 2001</em></p>
            <p>It's got a kooky vibe, it's fun! Somehow I thought it would kinda fun gameplay-wise but there's not too much to the gameplay apart from sucking up ghosts. E. Gadd is cute and some of the bosses were quite fun!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/luigi-mansion.webp">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Frankenstein</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>They decided to make Frankenstein hot and I don't understand why! I thought it was all pretty dumb. I guess it was entertaining</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/frankenstein.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Pink Flamingos</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1972</em></p>
            <p>Outrageous camp classic whose main goal is to be gross and horrible. It's hilarious and shocking and I have to say I preferred 'Female Trouble'</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/pink-flamingos.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Amrum</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>A gorgeous-looking film set during the German surrender in WW2 in a teeny-tiny island in north Germany. Fascinating glimpse into a time and place that I've never seen before. Simple/low-key plot but still engaging</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/amrum.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Kirby's Dream Buffet</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Totally wild that they went for this Kirby game! There are so many Kirby games and we got this random-ass spinoff?? Anyway, there are over 100 tracks here but it's fine because the majority of them are a jukebox of Kirby classics from other games, just like in Forgotten Land and Star Allies. Kirby soundtracks really do spoil us for throwbacks to old tunes. And through this we get to hear music from Nightmare in Dreamland, Super Star, Kirby's Dreamland 3... I hope they all get released too in their own time.<br>If nothing else, you can use this soundtrack as a nice Kirby playlist. The original tracks for the game itself are alright but a bit mid compared to Forgotten Land and Star Allies. There are a couple of surprise arrangements of old tracks which are quite good. Check out 'Revenge of Steel Wings' which reimagines Meta Knight's Revenge!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/kirby-dream-buffet.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Animal Crossing: New Leaf</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: 3DS, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I'm so delighted, so happy that this soundtrack has made it to the app! New Horizons is great but there is something extra special about this one.<br>When talking about Animal Crossing music you have to start with the hourly music that plays as you spend time in the game. This game's is minimal like Wild World, but much more refined and complex. There are more things going on, but it's still unafraid to use silence. Any more and it would sound like New Horizons with its bombastic synths and arguably too-loud hourly music. The combination of single accordion notes, glockenspiel, little bumps from a tuba, minimal piano, I dunno it just sounds dainty and lovely.<br>I feel like 1AM is an all-time classic, just a beautiful piano ballad. When you're playing Animal Crossing at 1AM you're almost definitely feeling wistful and this music reflects that. Other highlights for me are the space-y and delicate 7PM, which by the way has a 10/10 remix in smash, and the straight up bossa nova classic 5PM. Love love love.<br>Elsewhere in the soundtrack we've got some surprising bangers. I didn't realise that I missed the 'Shampoodle' music so much! I also never appreciated how perfect the 'GracieGrace' track is. And wild to think that all the Animal Crossing games have their own new year music. I really like this selection compared to New Horizons, especially the very peaceful New Year's Day.<br>Some tracks were done better in New Horizons (Festivale and Fireworks Show come to mind). I think Katrina's music might not be for everyone but I thoroughly enjoy that it's just a single note, and that this app lets you extend it for as long as you like.<br>Finally, special shout-outs to 'Town Tree', the unofficial Credits theme. It's gorgeous.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/animal-crossing-new-leaf.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>New Super Mario Bros</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: DS, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>At first glance you might think this soundtrack release would be a disappointment, but let me tell you this game has some hidden bangers in it. The credits theme alone is for me an all-time favourite track! It's a huge vibe. Then we were introduced to the timeless main theme with those 'bah!'s. In fact, all the music features the bahs in there and they are and remain iconic, because all the enemies in the game take a moment to pose whenever the sound comes.<br>Many tracks from for example the desert or beach levels have a different track to the later new super mario bros games, and I don't think they're better as such... but it's to hear something different. Those other themes did become stale after 3 games.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/new-super-mario-bros.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Metroid II - Return of Samus</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Gameboy, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow talk about unlistenable soundtracks on this app. You won't catch me ever listening to 'SR288 Area BGM 2' ever again, that's for sure. The gameboy soundchip really is a catastrophe. Most of the tracks are bleeps and bloops and that is actually what you hear during the game! The one exception is the excellent main theme.<br>I'm a little bit sad that they didn't release the 3DS remake as well, which contains some genuinely good tracks. I guess we were spoilt enough last time with Paper Mario and its remake. Another reminder not to feel entitled!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/metroid-2.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Trying new things</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/shibari2.jpg">
        

            <h2>Fun video for your entertainment</h2>
            <h3>Victreebel scream</h3>
            <p><em>Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yoOg5JYyFmA</em></p>
            <p>This is the sound that one of my favourite pokemon Victreebel makes</p>
            
        

            <h2>Smash character decoration in my house</h2>
            
            
            <p>A cool coaster I got from a convention featuring this banger Gameboy game Donkey Kong '94</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/misc/characters/deco/dk8.jpg">
        

            <h2>Smash character decoration in my house</h2>
            
            
            <p>A cool coaster I got from a convention with Daisy from her original game, Super Mario Land on the Gameboy</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/misc/characters/deco/daisy2.jpg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>Fantasy holiday in Mallorca</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-11-10-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hello friends and family, welcome to my second newsletter! If you are receiving a notification about this via RSS, do let me know! I'm curious to see if anyone actually subscribed. So far nobody I've spoken to actually wants to do that.<br>First I want to tell you guys about a cool new thing on my website. I've now got a section on the homepage with a daily music recommendation! I wanted to make something that changes every day so visiting the site becomes more interesting. I love music so I figured it would be great to give you guys specific tracks for you to listen to. I already have the very extensive 'Albums' and 'Nintendo Soundtracks' sections for your perusal, but this will focus on individual tracks. If you like them, don't be afraid to react to them with the new reactions feature.<br>My plan is to write them all in advance, and hopefully I'll be able to keep on top of them. If I run out of juice eventually I'll think of something else. As always I love it when you give me feedback about this kind of stuff.<br>What's been happening in my life lately? Victor and I had a beautiful holiday in Mallorca just this past week and it was incredible. If you know me, you know I talk about Mexico a lot, but the Mexican beaches have nothing on these beaches. Victor took me to all his favourite spots and it was stunning - I'm talking Super Mario Odyssey Seaside Kingdom vibes. One thing I struggled with there was presence of Germans on the island. They are causing many problems there and it was hard to admit that I live in Germany and love it there. I felt quite embarrassed for Germany when hanging out with the Mallorcans.<br>Otherwise my busy summer is hopefully coming to an end. I regret that I haven't made time for DJing with Weyes this summer, but I've been confronted with being unable to have it all many times this year. But at least I started a new book (Ursula K Le Guin's Earthsea). I look forward to spending more time this Autumn getting into that, completing Hollow Knight: Silksong, and listening to the crap out of the Paper Mario soundtrack. I've also randomly gotten really into doing the daily crossword on the Guardian news app. I've learned so many new words already!</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Hollow Knight: Silksong</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 10, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>I can't believe that after 7 years we actually got this game, and that it's as good as it is. Shoutouts to the dev team for ignoring the internet's feverish cries and instead taking their sweet time crafting the best metroidvania ever. They let this cook for as long as they needed - I mean they had all that money from the first game so why not! And the result is, they made a huge and beautiful game. And they sold it for just 20€! Incredible stuff. Defy the markets and do the right thing! I guess it's something you can only do as an indie studio if you make a legendary game like the first Hollow Knight.<br>Playing this has been a total pleasure because at the same time I've watched Victor play the first Hollow Knight. Watching him get immersed into the familiar world of Hollow Knight while I simultaneously jump into the brand new world of Silksong has been amazing because we can compare experiences. This game has so many moments of wonder as you discover a brand new area, desperately looking for a bench or a map.<br>In the game, you need to climb up what appears to be a mountain, which has a Citadel at the top. You already know there's gonna be a City of Tears-style ruined civilisation in that citadel and this game serves exactly that and SO MUCH MORE! And of course there is an equally rich and dense lore behind all these bugs and insects, just like in the first one. And you get to play as the cute and beautiful Hornet! She feels kinda different and I like it. I also love that she actually speaks! And not only that, but is well spoken. I'm done with silent protagonists. Bring me more protagonists like Hornet, who eloquently talk about smart stuff with NPCs. Yes.<br>Just like the original game, this game nails the vibe. There is a deep sadness in all of the caves. An almost dead civilisation dragging themselves towards some kind of inevitable doom. Some of the bugs have lost it already, some are nice but struggling. Some are making things work for them in the hellscape. The music reflects all that! The Bone Bottom music, the place where there is the least hope, is so desperately sad. Then you have the incredible Choral Chambers - wow! I haven't sat down to ask myself what kind of chord sequence that is yet but I am entranced. I also adore the music from Greyhome, and weirdly also the strangely beautiful Bilewater - somewhat unfitting music for such a horrible place.<br>This game will stay with me for a long time. It's an absolute gem! Some of the bosses are really hard but even though that Last Judge one really got me going, none of them have really been UNFAIR unfair. At least not yet. I haven't completed it 100% at the time of writing...</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/silksong.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Shoutouts to the Nintendo Music App team - they gave us one of the best video game soundtracks ever!!! I never thought they would actually release it because it's so lengthy. This thing is like 13 hours long! But here we are, it's here, and I've been pumping this music constantly all week.<br>Where do I start? They have not only faithfully remade all the old music, but they've taken it above and beyond what the original tracks were by using real instruments and adding new sections, extending the loops. The composers clearly did this with a lot of love and respect for the original. Vibes have been preserved!<br>The battle themes, already 10/10 in the original, now have new 'thinking' variants which are a lot of fun when listening in the game. I love that this has many things like this taken from Origami King (another fantastic soundtrack). Most importantly though, they made 8 different versions of the main battle theme! Huge! Even the few enemies you fight in the snowy area or the Riverside Station get their own music! I love it so much. There are new variations of Rogueport, which are great. And the new piano version of Poshley heights is so good!<br>Some great examples of extended loops are the 'Mario's House' music which is like twice as long, or 'Twilight Town' which has a beautiful new section. For Poshley Heights they added a jazz breakdown, why the fuck not. Professor Frankly's theme also goes super hard for no reason.<br>Some tracks just got elevated so much thanks to the new instrumentation. The Macho Grubba battle is suddenly the most intense track in the whole game, wow. The Palace Courtyard at the end of the game is another example. They also saved the otherwise horrible-sounding Gradus battle, and also same for the Pirate's Cave.<br>They also added new themes entirely for the partner characters and they sound just like Origami King. Even very minor characters get new music! New music for everyone! When did Ms. Mowz's theme go so hard?<br>There are a few remade tracks which don't live up the original, although it's hard for me to say why in some cases. Rogueport Underground doesn't speak to me so much. The Glitz Pit music has been revamped with an Erhu, this Chinese stringed instrument, giving it an oriental vibe which in opinion doesn't fit at all.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/paper-mario-ttyd-switch.avif">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Gamecube, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>What an incredible day. When we were brainstorming soundtracks that would be amazing on this app I hoped more than anything for this! I never truly believed this and its remake would come because of the sheer volume of tracks but here we are, Nintendo have delivered and I am delighted! This is one of my all-time favourite Nintendo soundtracks.<br>They've done RPGs before but none knock them out of the park quite like this one. For every moment in the game there is new music, resulting in wildly different vibes in different areas. And the games are not your usual Mario levels: desert, beach etc. Chapter 2 launches you into this insane 'Boggly Woods' area which feels more like an acid trip than anything else. The whole section is inspired by pikmin and I'm all for it. Then later you have the very melancholic Chapter 4 with the stunning Twilight Town music. Chapter 6 with its evening on the train vibe is also a 10/10. Then at the very end we are treated to the outstanding 'X-Naut Fortress', which is the biggest of all bops.<br>There is so much to enjoy here, and this is just the original Gamecube version! They also released the remake's music, which takes this base and goes to the moon with it. I will some of these original tracks are a little better than their remade counterparts. For example I have a soft spot for the Magnus von Grapple battle music in this version, same with Rogueport Sewers.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/paper-mario-ttyd.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Princess Peach: Showtime!</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This soundtrack joins Captain Toad as one of Nintendo's newer, generic soundtracks with little to offer. I guess there are too many games for Koji Kondo to preside over, they can't all be huge hits. I never played this game so I don't have any particular connection to its soundtrack. Listening to it makes me thing that it adheres to its relevant tropes without bringing anything special to the table. The wild west music is like stereotypical wild west, to the point where it's boring. This has nothing on Desert Kingdom from Mario Odyssey. That being said, I did really enjoy the spy music from the 'dashing thief' level.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/princess-peach-showtime.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Zelda II - The Adventure of Link</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: NES, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This game would be nothing if it weren't for that palace theme. The remix that made it into Melee's famous Hyrule Temple is timeless and is the sole reason people even know about this game. That song goes so hard it's insane. The Great Palace theme is also great but only half as long.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/zelda-2.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Beach from a postcard</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/beach.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Werd ich zum Augenblicke sagen: Verweile doch, du bist so schön!</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/verweile.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Painting date</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/marlo2.jpg">
        

            <h2>New Photo in the Gallery</h2>
            <h3>Honouring the sunflower with an appropriate stand</h3>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/gallery/belch.jpg">
        

            <h2>Fun video for your entertainment</h2>
            <h3>Pretty pathetic</h3>
            <p><em>Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQVgxPYBJzY</em></p>
            <p>Jessie from Pokemon is everything</p>
            
        

            <h2>Smash character decoration in my house</h2>
            
            
            <p>I got this at some convention and forgot about it until recently</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/misc/characters/deco/cloud1.jpg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>My first newsletter</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-23-09-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hello visitors to my website, welcome to my new newsletter! By popular demand, I have made available all the changes to the website as they come, you don't have to come and check it yourself every time.<br>It's currently September 2025, around 9 months since I started working on the website, so these newsletters won't contain stuff I wrote before then. I think that just means that there is a treasure trove of stuff on here for those who want to go diving. But at least you'll be informed on any new things I'm up to.<br>Working on this website has been such a highlight of the year. It's the first time I've ever actually enjoyed recreational programming! As an added bonus, I learned a ton about web development which is literally useful for my job.<br>2025 is making a strong case for being the best year of my life so far, which is very exciting. Getting a boyfriend, having an unforgettable trip to Mexico, and the release of the Nintendo Music App - so much magic has happened this year!<br>Anyway, here is a list of new things I've posted to the website recently. I'm not sure how often I will do these newsletters.</p>
            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>The Rogue Prince of Persia</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 3, Gameplay: 5, Platform: Xbox Gamepass, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Fab recommended me this game on his Gamepass and I gave it a go. It's a roguelite that's just the same as Dead Cells, which I never really played. I really didn't like the corporate vibe of the game. The music sounds like generic 'middle eastern' music for an epic blockbuster film. I also feel like the animations are a bit off. The artstyle is good though! They had a vision, that's for sure. But something about playing this while playing Silksong makes it feel so clunky and shit in comparison. I'm looking forward to playing Hades 2 later this year though!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/rogue-prince.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Donkey Kong '94</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 5, Gameplay: 7, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1994</em></p>
            <p>This gameboy game has a lot going for it! I've never seen a gameboy game with this many movement options. You can do cool flips if you change direction right before jumping, and you can jump on your head and hop off higher too. Then there are just a bunch of cool levels, like little puzzles to work through. It's honestly great.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/donkey-kong-94.png">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Blue Prince</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 10, Platform: Playstation 5, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Daaaaamn this game is so good! This is another one of those rare information games where you have to understand stuff about the lore and how things work in order to progress. I read somewhere people call them 'Metroidbrainias' which I thoroughly enjoy. Although this game is actually a roguelike! You go through a explore this mansion by drafting new rooms as you go. Each room is full of secrets about what's actually going on and it makes you want to learn everything about the game.<br>At the time of writing this I found the 46th room and decided to call it a day because the scope of the game is terrifying. I had many amazing eureka moments throughout my playthrough but one of them was learning about a crazy chess puzzle, thanks to happening to have the device you need to light candles on me when I finally got the basement key and was able to go down the fountain to the special area at the back. When I saw that those notes I had made about chess pieces in different rooms were about to be used... wait I have to draft them ALL? On top of this, my mate Rodrigo revealed at this point that he had over 150 hours in the game. For my sanity and my safety, I have to say no to the chess puzzle. I'll probably just get another sanctum key anyway, and that puzzle where I have to learn about all the history in order to make those sigils, my GOD. I wrote like 20 pages of notes for this, and I would have needed a new book to solve that one.<br>Anyway shout-outs to this game. So many highlights. I loved the logic puzzles, Alzara, the Aquarium puzzle, the computer system, the excitement of going to a brand new room. So much to enjoy!<br>I highly recommend this puzzle game! Puzzle games are the best!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/blue-prince.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>AirBlade</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 5, Gameplay: 3, Platform: PlayStation 2, Release: 2001</em></p>
            <p>I randomly remembered this old Tony Hawk's rip off that I played at some point when I was younger. I was so impressed that you could skateboard with a hoverboard! I thought it was a revolutionary idea. Looking back, it's literally just a normal skateboarding game.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/airblade.jpg">
        

            <h2>Game Review</h2>
            <h3>Desktop Destroyer</h3>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 1, Platform: PC, Release: 1999</em></p>
            <p>I saw an image of the hammer from this game and I was launched back into the past, kinda like when you smell something from your childhood and you have this moment where you are suddenly transported back. I used to love destroying my desktop with termites, flamethrowers and chainsaws and was endlessly entertained by it. It's a real blast from the past.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/games/desktop-destroyer.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Painted Boats</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1945</em></p>
            <p>Read about it in the Stoke Bruerne narrowboat museum when we had our boating holiday. Cool history lesson about life on canalboats before it became a tourism thing</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/painted-boats.jpg">
        

            <h2>Film Review</h2>
            <h3>Moonstruck</h3>
            <p><em>Release: 1987</em></p>
            <p>We watched this because it has Cher in it but were horrified when the heart-throb man on the film turned out to be horrible Nicolas Cage. Cher is beautiful but the film aged badly</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/films/moonstruck.png">
        

            <h2>Album Review</h2>
            <h3>Cancionera</h3>
            <p><em>Artist: Natalia Lafourcade, Release: 2025, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the albums page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow, after loving the previous album so much, here I am again, my world rocked from another Natalia record. In this one, it feels like she's playing the role of an alter-ego called 'cancionera'. Upon closer thought I realise she's talking to the version of herself which is a famous singer. Sometimes it feels like the songs are directed to another person but what if it's just her?<br>She's got these beautiful upbeat and happy songs like 'Cocos en la playa' which feel more like putting on a smiley face to deal with the sad feelings. It feels like she's coping. In fact that track feels more like a 'fuck this I'm going to the beach' because she's tired of social media and fame and all that shit. Instead she's gonna go smoke a joint on the beach, get naked and chat with the moon. 'El Coconito' is literally about wanting to feed corn to a turkey but there's no corn.<br>But she also bares all on the sad songs, which I love the most because I'm a sucker. 'Luna Cresciente' the perfect example: vibes-wise it feels like a huge black bird flying in the night. It's a song about longing and then sinks into this beautiful outro track. I love it. I love this whole album, it's different from the previous one but equally as stunning and the fun songs equally as fun. Each time I listen to it, I love it even more.<br>I've even gone and compiled a list of things I love most about each track - here they are!<br>Apertura Cancionera - starting off the album with 8 seconds of silence.<br>Cancionera - the part when the piano solo comes in, delicious.<br>Cocos en la Playa - the porrito reveal.<br>Como Quisiera Quererte - when she screams 'todas mis golondrinas van confudidas al mar!<br>Amor Clandestino - the switch from minor to major with the cheeky knowing looks on their faces.<br>Mascaritas de Cristal - when she leans forwards and gets to the point: 'quiero ver zu verdad'.<br>El Coconito - the gymnastics they do with their mouths on 'pero ahora no hay'.<br>El Palomo y La Negra - just that it's a party in the middle of the album.<br>Cariñito de Acapulco - when she calls out 'Ay mamita Guadalupe!!'.<br>La Bruja - singing 'me agarra la bruja' like she's about collapse.<br>Luna Creciente - 'borracha de amar' over the amazing 3 time guitar parts from Hermanos Gutierrez.<br>Lagrimas Cancionera - calm down with a lengthy orchestral piece, love when the voice comes in.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/albums/natalia-cancionera.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Donkey Kong Bananza</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch 2, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I was so shook when they released this special release of 9 tracks from the game as part of a promotion for the DLC on a Saturday! Talk about unpredictable. I can't help but ask myself why they didn't just release the whole soundtrack! Whatever, I need to move on. This game has some great bops in it. It's not on the level of Tropical Freeze but we do have the incredible Zebra Bananza at least.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/donkey-kong-bananza.jpg">
        

            <h2>Nintendo Soundtrack Review</h2>
            <h3>Super Mario Galaxy 2</h3>
            <p><em>Platform: Wii, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I didn't truly appreciate until this release that this soundtrack is largely orchestrated! It's a noticeable upgrade from the first game in many ways. Honestly when I was younger I didn't love this game as much as the first and I kinda slept on the soundtrack. Listening to some of Mario Kart World's remixes of these tracks opened my eyes to how great they are. For example, 'Yoshi Star Galaxy' is a huge bop, and you know what it was composed by none other than Koji Kondo! It all makes sense. Also, Digga-Leg is a total sleeper hit.<br>Otherwise this game features a lot of the same kinds of levels as the first one, a new beach level, a new fire/ice level, a new lava, desert level etc, and I'm impressed that they managed to write a different tune with the exact same vibe for them. There are also two secret peaceful tracks which have no right being as lovely as they are, 'World 3' and 'Slimy Spring Galaxy'. Little moments of beauty in the game, love it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/nintendo/super-mario-galaxy-2.png">
        

            <h2>Book Review</h2>
            <h3>1Q84</h3>
            <p><em>Author: Haruki Murakami, Release: 2009, for the spoiler discussion please visit the books page!</em></p>
            <p>This book is a gripping tale of two seemingly unrelated people living in a world where things don't quite seem right. Illogical things start happening, like a second moon appearing in the sky. What are you supposed to do when that happens and nobody is saying anything about it? From there the books descends into conceptual madness. There is some weird sex stuff but by the end you get used to it and realise it's part of the whole vibe. The characters are so extreme and the concepts so wild (I mean just look at the word 'Air Crysalis') that it's kinda hard to put down. It's all quite abstract and I'm honestly still trying to piece together what exactly it was about. I still really recommend it though, if nothing else but for the mental images it produces as you read it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/books/1q84.jpg">
        

            <h2>New CD</h2>
            <h3>There Existed an Addiction to Blood</h3>
            <p><em>Artist: Clipping.</em></p>
            <p>Very dark and harrowing hip-hop/noise music</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/albums/clipping-existed.jpg">
        

            <h2>New CD</h2>
            <h3>Wintersadness</h3>
            <p><em>Artist: G'Emma</em></p>
            <p>A friend in Berlin released this EP on CD! Got it at her concert in Kotti</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/music/albums/gemma-winter.jpg">
        

            <h2>Smash character decoration in my house</h2>
            
            
            <p>Whale got me this as a gift</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/images/misc/characters/deco/kazuya1.jpg">
        
<h3>And don't forget... an archive of "Soundtrack of the Day" updates are on the website!</h3>]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:45:53 +0053</pubDate></item></channel></rss>