<?xml version="1.0"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Fraser's Newsletter</title><link>https://worldpeace.services/newsletter</link><description>Welcome to my newsletter! I started making this website at the start of 2025 and I've enjoyed growing it to where it is today. I get that it's hard to constantly check the site for updates, so to make things easier for you guys, I've prepared a newsletter which features all the new content from the website whenever I update it. If you're struggling to read the RSS feed it\s fine, I get it. You can just read it directly on my website! https://worldpeace.services/newsletter</description><language>en</language><item><title>Fantasy holiday in Mallorca</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-11-10-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hello friends and family, welcome to my second newsletter! If you are receiving a notification about this via RSS, do let me know! I'm curious to see if anyone actually subscribed. So far nobody I've spoken to actually wants to do that.<br>First I want to tell you guys about a cool new thing on my website. I've now got a section on the homepage with a daily music recommendation! I wanted to make something that changes every day so visiting the site becomes more interesting. I love music so I figured it would be great to give you guys specific tracks for you to listen to. I already have the very extensive 'Albums' and 'Nintendo Soundtracks' sections for your perusal, but this will focus on individual tracks. If you like them, don't be afraid to react to them with the new reactions feature.<br>My plan is to write them all in advance, and hopefully I'll be able to keep on top of them. If I run out of juice eventually I'll think of something else. As always I love it when you give me feedback about this kind of stuff.<br>What's been happening in my life lately? Victor and I had a beautiful holiday in Mallorca just this past week and it was incredible. If you know me, you know I talk about Mexico a lot, but the Mexican beaches have nothing on these beaches. Victor took me to all his favourite spots and it was stunning - I'm talking Super Mario Odyssey Seaside Kingdom vibes. One thing I struggled with there was presence of Germans on the island. They are causing many problems there and it was hard to admit that I live in Germany and love it there. I felt quite embarrassed for Germany when hanging out with the Mallorcans.<br>Otherwise my busy summer is hopefully coming to an end. I regret that I haven't made time for DJing with Weyes this summer, but I've been confronted with being unable to have it all many times this year. But at least I started a new book (Ursula K Le Guin's Earthsea). I look forward to spending more time this Autumn getting into that, completing Hollow Knight: Silksong, and listening to the crap out of the Paper Mario soundtrack. I've also randomly gotten really into doing the daily crossword on the Guardian news app. I've learned so many new words already!</p>
            <h2>Hollow Knight: Silksong</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 10, Platform: Switch 2, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>I can't believe that after 7 years we actually got this game, and that it's as good as it is. Shoutouts to the dev team for ignoring the internet's feverish cries and instead taking their sweet time crafting the best metroidvania ever. They let this cook for as long as they needed - I mean they had all that money from the first game so why not! And the result is, they made a huge and beautiful game. And they sold it for just 20€! Incredible stuff. Defy the markets and do the right thing! I guess it's something you can only do as an indie studio if you make a legendary game like the first Hollow Knight.<br>Playing this has been a total pleasure because at the same time I've watched Victor play the first Hollow Knight. Watching him get immersed into the familiar world of Hollow Knight while I simultaneously jump into the brand new world of Silksong has been amazing because we can compare experiences. This game has so many moments of wonder as you discover a brand new area, desperately looking for a bench or a map.<br>In the game, you need to climb up what appears to be a mountain, which has a Citadel at the top. You already know there's gonna be a City of Tears-style ruined civilisation in that citadel and this game serves exactly that and SO MUCH MORE! And of course there is an equally rich and dense lore behind all these bugs and insects, just like in the first one. And you get to play as the cute and beautiful Hornet! She feels kinda different and I like it. I also love that she actually speaks! And not only that, but is well spoken. I'm done with silent protagonists. Bring me more protagonists like Hornet, who eloquently talk about smart stuff with NPCs. Yes.<br>Just like the original game, this game nails the vibe. There is a deep sadness in all of the caves. An almost dead civilisation dragging themselves towards some kind of inevitable doom. Some of the bugs have lost it already, some are nice but struggling. Some are making things work for them in the hellscape. The music reflects all that! The Bone Bottom music, the place where there is the least hope, is so desperately sad. Then you have the incredible Choral Chambers - wow! I haven't sat down to ask myself what kind of chord sequence that is yet but I am entranced. I also adore the music from Greyhome, and weirdly also the strangely beautiful Bilewater - somewhat unfitting music for such a horrible place.<br>This game will stay with me for a long time. It's an absolute gem! Some of the bosses are really hard but even though that Last Judge one really got me going, none of them have really been UNFAIR unfair. At least not yet. I haven't completed it 100% at the time of writing...</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/silksong.jpg" alt="Hollow Knight: Silksong">
        

            <h2>Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>Shoutouts to the Nintendo Music App team - they gave us one of the best video game soundtracks ever!!! I never thought they would actually release it because it's so lengthy. This thing is like 13 hours long! But here we are, it's here, and I've been pumping this music constantly all week.<br>Where do I start? They have not only faithfully remade all the old music, but they've taken it above and beyond what the original tracks were by using real instruments and adding new sections, extending the loops. The composers clearly did this with a lot of love and respect for the original. Vibes have been preserved!<br>The battle themes, already 10/10 in the original, now have new 'thinking' variants which are a lot of fun when listening in the game. I love that this has many things like this taken from Origami King (another fantastic soundtrack). Most importantly though, they made 8 different versions of the main battle theme! Huge! Even the few enemies you fight in the snowy area or the Riverside Station get their own music! I love it so much. There are new variations of Rogueport, which are great. And the new piano version of Poshley heights is so good!<br>Some great examples of extended loops are the 'Mario's House' music which is like twice as long, or 'Twilight Town' which has a beautiful new section. For Poshley Heights they added a jazz breakdown, why the fuck not. Professor Frankly's theme also goes super hard for no reason.<br>Some tracks just got elevated so much thanks to the new instrumentation. The Macho Grubba battle is suddenly the most intense track in the whole game, wow. The Palace Courtyard at the end of the game is another example. They also saved the otherwise horrible-sounding Gradus battle, and also same for the Pirate's Cave.<br>They also added new themes entirely for the partner characters and they sound just like Origami King. Even very minor characters get new music! New music for everyone! When did Ms. Mowz's theme go so hard?<br>There are a few remade tracks which don't live up the original, although it's hard for me to say why in some cases. Rogueport Underground doesn't speak to me so much. The Glitz Pit music has been revamped with an Erhu, this Chinese stringed instrument, giving it an oriental vibe which in opinion doesn't fit at all.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/paper-mario-ttyd-switch.avif" alt="Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door">
        

            <h2>Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: Gamecube, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>What an incredible day. When we were brainstorming soundtracks that would be amazing on this app I hoped more than anything for this! I never truly believed this and its remake would come because of the sheer volume of tracks but here we are, Nintendo have delivered and I am delighted! This is one of my all-time favourite Nintendo soundtracks.<br>They've done RPGs before but none knock them out of the park quite like this one. For every moment in the game there is new music, resulting in wildly different vibes in different areas. And the games are not your usual Mario levels: desert, beach etc. Chapter 2 launches you into this insane 'Boggly Woods' area which feels more like an acid trip than anything else. The whole section is inspired by pikmin and I'm all for it. Then later you have the very melancholic Chapter 4 with the stunning Twilight Town music. Chapter 6 with its evening on the train vibe is also a 10/10. Then at the very end we are treated to the outstanding 'X-Naut Fortress', which is the biggest of all bops.<br>There is so much to enjoy here, and this is just the original Gamecube version! They also released the remake's music, which takes this base and goes to the moon with it. I will some of these original tracks are a little better than their remade counterparts. For example I have a soft spot for the Magnus von Grapple battle music in this version, same with Rogueport Sewers.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/paper-mario-ttyd.jpg" alt="Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door">
        

            <h2>Princess Peach: Showtime!</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This soundtrack joins Captain Toad as one of Nintendo's newer, generic soundtracks with little to offer. I guess there are too many games for Koji Kondo to preside over, they can't all be huge hits. I never played this game so I don't have any particular connection to its soundtrack. Listening to it makes me thing that it adheres to its relevant tropes without bringing anything special to the table. The wild west music is like stereotypical wild west, to the point where it's boring. This has nothing on Desert Kingdom from Mario Odyssey. That being said, I did really enjoy the spy music from the 'dashing thief' level.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/princess-peach-showtime.jpg" alt="Princess Peach: Showtime!">
        

            <h2>Zelda II - The Adventure of Link</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: NES, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>This game would be nothing if it weren't for that palace theme. The remix that made it into Melee's famous Hyrule Temple is timeless and is the sole reason people even know about this game. That song goes so hard it's insane. The Great Palace theme is also great but only half as long.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/zelda-2.jpg" alt="Zelda II - The Adventure of Link">
        

            <h2>Beach from a postcard</h2>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/gallery/beach.jpg" alt="Beach from a postcard">
        

            <h2>Werd ich zum Augenblicke sagen: Verweile doch, du bist so schön!</h2>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/gallery/verweile.jpg" alt="Werd ich zum Augenblicke sagen: Verweile doch, du bist so schön!">
        

            <h2>Painting date</h2>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/gallery/marlo2.jpg" alt="Painting date">
        

            <h2>Honouring the sunflower with an appropriate stand</h2>
            <p><em>For anecdotes about the pictures, please visit the gallery page!</em></p>
            <p>None</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/gallery/belch.jpg" alt="Honouring the sunflower with an appropriate stand">
        

            <h2>Pretty pathetic</h2>
            <p><em>Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQVgxPYBJzY</em></p>
            <p>Jessie from Pokemon is everything</p>
            
        

            <h2>None</h2>
            <p><em>None</em></p>
            <p>I got this at some convention and forgot about it until recently</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/misc/characters/deco/cloud1.jpg" alt="None">
        

            <h2>X-Naut Fortress</h2>
            <p><em>Composer: Yoshito Hirano, Yuka Tsujiyoko, Game: Paper Mario: The Thousand Year Door, Day: 11-10-2025, Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rfvpEOROQo8</em></p>
            <p>Today I'm celebrating this game's release on the Nintendo Music App with this absolute banger from the Gamecube. It's one of Nintendo's only dance bangers and who knows maybe it will find itself in a DJ World Peace set one day.</p>
            
        

            <h2>Cocos en la Playa</h2>
            <p><em>Artist: Natalia Lafourcade, Album: Cancionera, Day: 10-10-2025, Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7a0pq4KYKwQ</em></p>
            <p>Welcome to the first soundtrack of the day! I'll use this space to recommend you some great music to enjoy every single day! Today I wanna highlight one of my all-time favourite artists Natalia and this song all about fucking off because she's had enough. Say no to screens, likes, annoying real-life shit and just go to the beach, get naked and swim in the sea and chat with the moon. The sigh right before the porrito reveal says it all.</p>
            
        ]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0053</pubDate></item><item><title>My first newsletter</title><link>https://your.newsletter.site/newsletters/newsletter-23-09-2025</link><description><![CDATA[<p>Hello visitors to my website, welcome to my new newsletter! By popular demand, I have made available all the changes to the website as they come, you don't have to come and check it yourself every time.<br>It's currently September 2025, around 9 months since I started working on the website, so these newsletters won't contain stuff I wrote before then. I think that just means that there is a treasure trove of stuff on here for those who want to go diving. But at least you'll be informed on any new things I'm up to.<br>Working on this website has been such a highlight of the year. It's the first time I've ever actually enjoyed recreational programming! As an added bonus, I learned a ton about web development which is literally useful for my job.<br>2025 is making a strong case for being the best year of my life so far, which is very exciting. Getting a boyfriend, having an unforgettable trip to Mexico, and the release of the Nintendo Music App - so much magic has happened this year!<br>Anyway, here is a list of new things I've posted to the website recently. I'm not sure how often I will do these newsletters.</p>
            <h2>The Rogue Prince of Persia</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 3, Gameplay: 5, Platform: Xbox Gamepass, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Fab recommended me this game on his Gamepass and I gave it a go. It's a roguelite that's just the same as Dead Cells, which I never really played. I really didn't like the corporate vibe of the game. The music sounds like generic 'middle eastern' music for an epic blockbuster film. I also feel like the animations are a bit off. The artstyle is good though! They had a vision, that's for sure. But something about playing this while playing Silksong makes it feel so clunky and shit in comparison. I'm looking forward to playing Hades 2 later this year though!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/rogue-prince.jpg" alt="The Rogue Prince of Persia">
        

            <h2>Donkey Kong '94</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 5, Gameplay: 7, Platform: Gameboy, Release: 1994</em></p>
            <p>This gameboy game has a lot going for it! I've never seen a gameboy game with this many movement options. You can do cool flips if you change direction right before jumping, and you can jump on your head and hop off higher too. Then there are just a bunch of cool levels, like little puzzles to work through. It's honestly great.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/donkey-kong-94.png" alt="Donkey Kong '94">
        

            <h2>Blue Prince</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 10, Gameplay: 10, Platform: Playstation 5, Release: 2025</em></p>
            <p>Daaaaamn this game is so good! This is another one of those rare information games where you have to understand stuff about the lore and how things work in order to progress. I read somewhere people call them 'Metroidbrainias' which I thoroughly enjoy. Although this game is actually a roguelike! You go through a explore this mansion by drafting new rooms as you go. Each room is full of secrets about what's actually going on and it makes you want to learn everything about the game.<br>At the time of writing this I found the 46th room and decided to call it a day because the scope of the game is terrifying. I had many amazing eureka moments throughout my playthrough but one of them was learning about a crazy chess puzzle, thanks to happening to have the device you need to light candles on me when I finally got the basement key and was able to go down the fountain to the special area at the back. When I saw that those notes I had made about chess pieces in different rooms were about to be used... wait I have to draft them ALL? On top of this, my mate Rodrigo revealed at this point that he had over 150 hours in the game. For my sanity and my safety, I have to say no to the chess puzzle. I'll probably just get another sanctum key anyway, and that puzzle where I have to learn about all the history in order to make those sigils, my GOD. I wrote like 20 pages of notes for this, and I would have needed a new book to solve that one.<br>Anyway shout-outs to this game. So many highlights. I loved the logic puzzles, Alzara, the Aquarium puzzle, the computer system, the excitement of going to a brand new room. So much to enjoy!<br>I highly recommend this puzzle game! Puzzle games are the best!</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/blue-prince.jpg" alt="Blue Prince">
        

            <h2>AirBlade</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 5, Gameplay: 3, Platform: PlayStation 2, Release: 2001</em></p>
            <p>I randomly remembered this old Tony Hawk's rip off that I played at some point when I was younger. I was so impressed that you could skateboard with a hoverboard! I thought it was a revolutionary idea. Looking back, it's literally just a normal skateboarding game.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/airblade.jpg" alt="AirBlade">
        

            <h2>Desktop Destroyer</h2>
            <p><em>Vibes: 9, Gameplay: 1, Platform: PC, Release: 1999</em></p>
            <p>I saw an image of the hammer from this game and I was launched back into the past, kinda like when you smell something from your childhood and you have this moment where you are suddenly transported back. I used to love destroying my desktop with termites, flamethrowers and chainsaws and was endlessly entertained by it. It's a real blast from the past.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/games/desktop-destroyer.jpg" alt="Desktop Destroyer">
        

            <h2>Painted Boats</h2>
            <p><em>Release: 1945</em></p>
            <p>Read about it in the Stoke Bruerne narrowboat museum when we had our boating holiday. Cool history lesson about life on canalboats before it became a tourism thing</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/films/painted-boats.jpg" alt="Painted Boats">
        

            <h2>Moonstruck</h2>
            <p><em>Release: 1987</em></p>
            <p>We watched this because it has Cher in it but were horrified when the heart-throb man on the film turned out to be horrible Nicolas Cage. Cher is beautiful but the film aged badly</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/films/moonstruck.png" alt="Moonstruck">
        

            <h2>Cancionera</h2>
            <p><em>Artist: Natalia Lafourcade, Release: 2025, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the albums page!</em></p>
            <p>Wow, after loving the previous album so much, here I am again, my world rocked from another Natalia record. In this one, it feels like she's playing the role of an alter-ego called 'cancionera'. Upon closer thought I realise she's talking to the version of herself which is a famous singer. Sometimes it feels like the songs are directed to another person but what if it's just her?<br>She's got these beautiful upbeat and happy songs like 'Cocos en la playa' which feel more like putting on a smiley face to deal with the sad feelings. It feels like she's coping. In fact that track feels more like a 'fuck this I'm going to the beach' because she's tired of social media and fame and all that shit. Instead she's gonna go smoke a joint on the beach, get naked and chat with the moon. 'El Coconito' is literally about wanting to feed corn to a turkey but there's no corn.<br>But she also bares all on the sad songs, which I love the most because I'm a sucker. 'Luna Cresciente' the perfect example: vibes-wise it feels like a huge black bird flying in the night. It's a song about longing and then sinks into this beautiful outro track. I love it. I love this whole album, it's different from the previous one but equally as stunning and the fun songs equally as fun. Each time I listen to it, I love it even more.<br>I've even gone and compiled a list of things I love most about each track - here they are!<br>Apertura Cancionera - starting off the album with 8 seconds of silence.<br>Cancionera - the part when the piano solo comes in, delicious.<br>Cocos en la Playa - the porrito reveal.<br>Como Quisiera Quererte - when she screams 'todas mis golondrinas van confudidas al mar!<br>Amor Clandestino - the switch from minor to major with the cheeky knowing looks on their faces.<br>Mascaritas de Cristal - when she leans forwards and gets to the point: 'quiero ver zu verdad'.<br>El Coconito - the gymnastics they do with their mouths on 'pero ahora no hay'.<br>El Palomo y La Negra - just that it's a party in the middle of the album.<br>Cariñito de Acapulco - when she calls out 'Ay mamita Guadalupe!!'.<br>La Bruja - singing 'me agarra la bruja' like she's about collapse.<br>Luna Creciente - 'borracha de amar' over the amazing 3 time guitar parts from Hermanos Gutierrez.<br>Lagrimas Cancionera - calm down with a lengthy orchestral piece, love when the voice comes in.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/albums/natalia-cancionera.jpg" alt="Cancionera">
        

            <h2>Donkey Kong Bananza</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: Switch 2, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I was so shook when they released this special release of 9 tracks from the game as part of a promotion for the DLC on a Saturday! Talk about unpredictable. I can't help but ask myself why they didn't just release the whole soundtrack! Whatever, I need to move on. This game has some great bops in it. It's not on the level of Tropical Freeze but we do have the incredible Zebra Bananza at least.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/donkey-kong-bananza.jpg" alt="Donkey Kong Bananza">
        

            <h2>Super Mario Galaxy 2</h2>
            <p><em>Platform: Wii, for a list of favourite tracks, please visit the nintendo soundtracks page!</em></p>
            <p>I didn't truly appreciate until this release that this soundtrack is largely orchestrated! It's a noticeable upgrade from the first game in many ways. Honestly when I was younger I didn't love this game as much as the first and I kinda slept on the soundtrack. Listening to some of Mario Kart World's remixes of these tracks opened my eyes to how great they are. For example, 'Yoshi Star Galaxy' is a huge bop, and you know what it was composed by none other than Koji Kondo! It all makes sense. Also, Digga-Leg is a total sleeper hit.<br>Otherwise this game features a lot of the same kinds of levels as the first one, a new beach level, a new fire/ice level, a new lava, desert level etc, and I'm impressed that they managed to write a different tune with the exact same vibe for them. There are also two secret peaceful tracks which have no right being as lovely as they are, 'World 3' and 'Slimy Spring Galaxy'. Little moments of beauty in the game, love it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/nintendo/super-mario-galaxy-2.png" alt="Super Mario Galaxy 2">
        

            <h2>1Q84</h2>
            <p><em>Author: Haruki Murakami, Release: 2009, for the spoiler discussion please visit the books page!</em></p>
            <p>This book is a gripping tale of two seemingly unrelated people living in a world where things don't quite seem right. Illogical things start happening, like a second moon appearing in the sky. What are you supposed to do when that happens and nobody is saying anything about it? From there the books descends into conceptual madness. There is some weird sex stuff but by the end you get used to it and realise it's part of the whole vibe. The characters are so extreme and the concepts so wild (I mean just look at the word 'Air Crysalis') that it's kinda hard to put down. It's all quite abstract and I'm honestly still trying to piece together what exactly it was about. I still really recommend it though, if nothing else but for the mental images it produces as you read it.</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/books/1q84.jpg" alt="1Q84">
        

            <h2>There Existed an Addiction to Blood</h2>
            <p><em>Artist: Clipping.</em></p>
            <p>Very dark and harrowing hip-hop/noise music</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/albums/clipping-existed.jpg" alt="There Existed an Addiction to Blood">
        

            <h2>Wintersadness</h2>
            <p><em>Artist: G'Emma</em></p>
            <p>A friend in Berlin released this EP on CD! Got it at her concert in Kotti</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/music/albums/gemma-winter.jpg" alt="Wintersadness">
        

            <h2>None</h2>
            <p><em>None</em></p>
            <p>Whale got me this as a gift</p>
            <img src="https://worldpeace.services/assets/misc/characters/deco/kazuya1.jpg" alt="None">
        ]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0053</pubDate></item></channel></rss>